<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://cxzaqwed.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://cxzaqwed.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-10-21T07:31:01+00:00</updated><id>https://cxzaqwed.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">cxzaqwed</title><subtitle>I like to know how everything works on this simulation called &quot;life&quot;. I test, explore, create, and everything else that Science help us to do.
</subtitle><author><name>cxzaqwed</name></author><entry><title type="html">A short story about me</title><link href="https://cxzaqwed.github.io/2020/10/20/story-about-me.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A short story about me" /><published>2020-10-20T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-10-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://cxzaqwed.github.io/2020/10/20/story-about-me</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://cxzaqwed.github.io/2020/10/20/story-about-me.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;wake-up-neo&quot;&gt;wake up, Neo!&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like to know how everything works on this simulation called “life”.&lt;br /&gt;
At my 6 years old, in a beautiful day on my class, i’ve found something strange under my desk. It was a CD-ROM of Animatrix film. I’ve searched for the owner, but i couldn’t find him, so i have take the CD to my home. I never heard about Matrix, but the CD had some information about the history, but in English.&lt;br /&gt;
-“how can i read this?”. I thought.&lt;br /&gt;
So i ran to my bedroom and looked for an English dictionary that i own from my mom, and translated the CD history, word by word, and at the end, i have discovered a new world, the world of the electron and the switch, the world out of that meets the eye.&lt;br /&gt;
Some years later, because of this CD, my computer won a new meaning: A door, that when it’s open to the world, can show all the humanity knowledge, from any time, from anywhere, about anything, like the Neo from Matrix, we can do everything in this world. But how it works? We can really enter anywhere? Read everything? How the computer works?&lt;br /&gt;
Since that, i keep myself searching, for unseen knowledge, locked doors, secret places, because that is my hobby, and The “Matrix” is my lab.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>cxzaqwed</name></author><category term="story" /><category term="EN" /><summary type="html">wake up, Neo!</summary></entry></feed>